http://www.aacb.asn.au/privacypolicy

Profile
Annual General MeetingAGM Minutes, Agendas and Associated Papers
Glossary
Guidelines & Position StatementsGuidelines and Position Statements
EventsCalendar
Annual Scientific ConferenceAACB 57th Annual Scientific Conference
RCPA AACB Chemical Pathology CoursePurchase Course Notes
Course Notes (Members Only)
Webinar Series2020 Webinars (member log-in required)
2019 Webinars (member log-in required)
2018 Webinars (member login required)
2017 Webinars(member login required)
2016 Webinars (member login required)
Branch Educational Presentations
Omniscience Clinical Case Studies LibraryOmniscience Clinical Case Studies by Topic
Strategic Plan 2019-22
AACB CommitteesScientific and Regulatory Affairs CommitteeMembership of SRAC
AACB RCPAQAP Advisory CommitteesAccuracy and Standardisation
Education Committee
Media and Communications CommitteeThe Clinical Biochemist Reviews
Contact Us
Education & CPDExaminations & CurriculumCurriculumAnalytical Biochemistry
RCPA AACB Chemical Pathology CoursePurchase Course Notes
Course Notes (Members Only)
Webinar Series2020 Webinars (member log-in required)
2019 Webinars (member log-in required)
2018 Webinars (member login required)
2017 Webinars(member login required)
2016 Webinars (member login required)
Branch Educational Presentations
Omniscience Clinical Case Studies LibraryOmniscience Clinical Case Studies by Topic
EventsCalendar
Annual Scientific ConferenceAACB 57th Annual Scientific ConferenceScientific Program
Glossary
Guidelines & Position StatementsGuidelines and Position Statements
Profile
Annual General MeetingAGM Minutes, Agendas and Associated Papers
CBN: Clinical Biochemist Newsletter
Publications ArchiveClinical Biochemist Reviews Volumes 1-23
Introduction
The Australasian Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine Inc (AACB) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.
AACB has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices which apply to all transactions made through www.aacb.asn.au.
Who we are?
The AACB data controller is the Chief Executive Officer. You may contact them with any concerns regarding this privacy statement or your personal data by e-mail at ceo@aacb.asn.au
What information do we collect?
AACB does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from the registration process for subscription or services and in connection with membership, content submissions, community postings (e.g., forums), suggestions and transactional areas.
Sensitive financial information such as credit card details are not stored in our database and transactions are processed through a secure gateway.
How do we use personal information?
The personal information you supply to us is used for membership account setup and administration, event registrations, and examination registrations. You may choose to make your contact details available in the online Member Directory and can opt-out at any time. Access to the directory is only available to members
At the time of collection you will have the opportunity to indicate whether you would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings.
What legal basis do we have for processing your personal data?
AACB holds and processes your personal data with your consent. You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting the AACB, office@aacb.asn.au and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from the database.
When do we share personal data?
Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.
We may share limited personal details with third parties such as professional conference organisers in order to provide appropriate services such as conference registrations or accommodation.
Where do we store and process personal data?
Personal data collected by AACB is held within our Associations Online membership database supplied and maintained by ASI (Advanced Solutions International). ASI holds all personal data on secure servers and further information can be found here: https://www.advsol.com/ASI/iMIS20/about/legal.aspx. No personal details are stored on AACB computers or cloud storage drives.
How do we secure personal data?
Access to the database containing personal information is restricted to AACB staff members with direct responsibility for customer service or management of the website. Access is password protected and subject to audit trail and all staff are trained in their responsibilities under this privacy policy.
How long do we keep your personal data for?
Your personal data is retained by AACB for up to two years from the date of your most recent contact. At the end of this time period AACB will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from the database.
Your rights in relation to personal data
We respect your right to access and control your personal data. Users can update their personal details through the Members Centre.
Where requested we will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted which the user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests.
How to contact us?
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact :
AACB Office
Unit 5, 85 Bourke Road, Alexandria NSW 2015
Telephone: 02 9669 6600
Fax: 02 9669 6607
Email: office@aacb.asn.au
AACB reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Australasian Association for Clinical Biochemistry and Laboratory Medicine Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Site Map | Contact Us
Association Online
Affiliations:
